Adventures of a time traveling elf
Saving Santa is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Aaron Seelman.
A lowly stable elf finds that he is the only one who can stop an invasion of the North Pole by using
the secret of Santa's Sleigh, a TimeGlobe, to travel back in time to Save Santa - twice.
Bernard D. Elf (voice), played by Martin Freeman.
Neville Baddington (voice), played by Tim Curry.
Santa (voice), played by Tim Conway.
Mrs. Claus (voice), played by Pam Ferris.
Shiny (voice), played by Ashley French.
Vera Baddington (voice), played by Joan Collins.
Saving Santa is a 2013 animated Christmas comedy film created and written by Tony Nottage and
directed by Leon Joosen, produced by Tony Nottage, Terry Stone, and Nick Simunek.
The film was released direct-to-video.
The film explores themes of elves, santa claus, time travel, musical, reindeer.
The tone is lighthearted.